Narrator: 1
Speaker 1: Are you feeling better?
Speaker 2: Yes, I think I’ll go back to work tomorrow.
Narrator: 2
Speaker 1: The shirt you bought me is too small.
Speaker 2: Don’t worry.
I’ll take it back to the shop and change it.
I still have the receipt.
Narrator: 3
Speaker 1: Hi, Jack.
It’s me, Karen.
Speaker 2: I can’t talk now, I’m in a Zoom meeting – I’ll call you back in 15 minutes.
Narrator: 4
Speaker 1: That’s my pen you’re using!
Speaker 2: Is it? Sorry.
I’ll give it back in a minute.
Narrator: 5
Speaker 1: Can you lend me £20? I’ll pay you back next week.
Speaker 2: OK – I’ll ping it to you.
Narrator: 6
Speaker 1: Where did you buy those shoes?
Speaker 2: I ordered them from Zara, but they’re too big.
I think I’ll send them back.